javarevisited.blogspot.in 2019-12-17

# Privacy Policy

**Who We Are:**  
Our blog address is [http://javarevisited.blogspot.com](http://javarevisited.blogspot.com/). This is my personal blog where I share about Java and Programming, my personal experience with free of cost. We don't charge anything to the reader for reading our articles.

###  What personal data we collect and why we collect it

###  **Comments**

When a reader leaves comments on this blog Blogger may collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.

The blog is powered by Google's blogger.com content management system and all privacy policy of them applied to this blog as well, you can read more about their privacy policy on <https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en>

###  **Cookies**

If you leave a comment on our site Google may save your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last until Blogger or Google thinks, usually a month to a year.

If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.

###  **Embedded content from other websites**

Articles on this site may include embedded content (like links, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.

These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracking your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.

###  Caching

This site may utilize caching in order to facilitate a faster response time and better user experience. Caching potentially stores a duplicate copy of every web page that is on display on this site.

All cache files are temporary and are never accessed by any third party, except as necessary to obtain technical support from the cache plugin vendor. Cache files expire on a schedule set by the site administrator, but may easily be purged by the admin before their natural expiration, if necessary.

###  Analytics

We use Google Analytics to track traffic, we don’t hold any data at our servers.  
If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely or until Google or Blogger decides to keep it. See <https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en> for more information  
.

**Disclaimer**  
The contents of this report are based on information generally available to the public from sources believed to be reliable.

No representation is made that it is timely, accurate or complete. Javarevisited has taken due care and caution in compilation of data as this has been obtained from various sources including which it considers reliable and first hand.

However, javarevisited.blogspot.com does not guarantee the accuracy, adequacy or completeness of any information and it is not responsible for any errors or omissions or for the results obtained from the use of such information and especially states that it has no financial liability whatsoever to the subscribers/users of this report.

The information herein, together with all estimates and forecasts, can change without notice.

This report does not purport to be a solicitation of any advice pertaining to trade and business and readers are advised to consult experts or study/evaluate individual business prospectus and other relevant legal documents before taking any decisions based on information provided in the site.

Neither javarevisited.blogspot.com nor its Editors or Authors accept any liability whatsoever nor do they accept responsibility for any financial consequences arising from the use of the research or information provided herein.

**Privacy Policy**  
We understand the importance of your privacy as a visitor to this website. We want you to understand how the information you may provide will be used.

To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining some online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used.

To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

I also suggest you visit the blogger's privacy policy which  is applicable here because this blog is powered by blogger:  <https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en>

###  **Information collected**

[Javarevisited](https://www.java67.com/) does not collect personal information about you except for the information that you voluntarily provide. We may collect usage information of our site to analyze interest in content and to provide advertisers information on an aggregate basis. No personally identifiable information will be shared with third-party advertising companies.

###  **Google Adsense and the DoubleClick DART Cookie**

Google, as a third party advertisement vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site. The use of DART cookies by Google enables them to serve adverts to visitors that are based on their visits to this website as well as other sites on the internet.

To opt out of the DART cookies you may visit the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL [http://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads](https://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/) Tracking of users through the DART cookie mechanisms are subject to Google’s own privacy policies.

Other Third Party ad servers or ad networks may also use cookies to track users activities on this website to measure advertisement effectiveness and other reasons that will be provided in their own privacy policies, Javarevisited has no access or control over these cookies that may be used by third party advertisers.

###  **Links to third party Websites**

We have included links on this site for your use and reference.  We are not responsible for the privacy policies on these websites. You should be aware that the privacy policies of these sites may differ from our own.

###  **Changes to this Privacy Statement**

The contents of this statement may be altered at any time, at our discretion.

If you have any questions regarding the privacy policy of javarevisited then you may contact me through via email on savingfunda@gmail.com.
